# Duc (David) Le

# Full Stack Engineer

wa.me/+84973877428

☑ ducqhle@gmail.com

in linkedin.com/in/ducqhle

ducqhle.github.io

## **Summary**

4 years of experience developing highly interactive applications using the latest web technologies. Contributed to more than 5 projects at world class had SEO optimized, high interactive UX/UI, great performance and full responsive. Not only by getting the task done but also constantly looking for ways to make it better. A long life leaner with the mindset that technology is to solving problems.

# Work experience

#### **Full Stack Engineer**

2021-01 - present

Spiderbox Design

- Developed full responsive UI in various applications using different cutting edge technologies, included but not limited to ReactJS, TypeScript, NextJS, Formik, Yup, React Emotion, Material-UI, .NET Core.
- Actively reviewed code and supported across multiple teams.
- Investigated many complex front-end issues which required deep codebase knowledge and library API specifications (Ag-grid, MobX, Upgrade Material-UI version).
- Created the schedule and agenda for the React|S internship program.
- On-boarded new members with the front-end systems.

# **Software Engineer** 2020-07 - 2021-01

Ubitec

- Participated in maintaining and developing the core features for the chatbot-platform with ReactJS, NodeJS, TypeScript, Microsoft Bot Framework, React Flow, Redux.
- Researched solutions in order to implement chatbot application requirements and systems required specifications.
- Added new code while keeping the code's coverage by include it along with the unit test which powered by Jest, React Testing Library and Fast Check.
- Configured CI/CD process using Jenkins, Docker, and integrate with Bitbucket, OpenShift.

### **Software Engineer** 2018-09 - 2020-04

KMS Technology, Inc

- Developed end-to-end features, investigated issues full flow from back-end (.NET, NodeJS), database (MSQL) to front-end (ASP.NET).
- Migrated a .NET legacy system from monolith to cloud base service by using AWS Lambda, .NET core and NodelS.
- Built a AI chatbot assistant powered by Microsoft Cognitive Services and Microsoft Bot Framework to help administration team supporting employees with the knowledge base building around the FAQ documents.

#### **Education**

#### Bachelor's degree, Technology Information

2015-09 - 2018-06

University of Science

#### **Certifications**

- Udemy Certificate of Completion Learn and Understand NodeJS Udemy
- React The Complete Guide (incl Hooks, React Router, Redux) Udemy
- The Complete Guide to Advanced React Component Patterns Udemy